<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">LaunderUp Partners</string>
    <string name="launder_up" translatable="false">Launder Up</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select Language</string>
    <string name="hindi">Hindi</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="go_to_back_screen">Go to Back Screen</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="otp_verification">Verification Code</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend Otp</string>
    <string name="_50_sec"> In 50 Sec</string>
    <string name="shop_details">Shop Details</string>
    <string name="shop_information">Shop Information</string>
    <string name="shop_name">Shop Name</string>
    <string name="shop_address">Shop Address</string>
    <string name="contact_number_at_shop">Contact Number at Shop</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="shop_owner_details">Shop Owner Details</string>
    <string name="same_as_shop_mobile_number">Same as Shop Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="shop_owner_email_address">Shop Owner Email Address</string>
    <string name="shop_owner_full_name">Shop Owner Full Name</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="shop_timings">Shop Timings</string>
    <string name="shop_operational_hours">Shop Operational Hours</string>
    <string name="opens_at">Opens at</string>
    <string name="closes_at">Closes at</string>
    <string name="click_to_choose_open_timing">Click to choose Open Timing</string>
    <string name="click_to_choose_close_timings">Click to Choose Close timings</string>
    <string name="_00_00">00:00</string>
    <string name="mark_open_days">Mark Open Days</string>
    <string name="monday">Monday</string>
    <string name="friday">Friday</string>
    <string name="tuesday">Tuesday</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="wednesday">Wednesday</string>
    <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="thursday">Thursday</string>
    <string name="shop_types_and_cloths">Shop Types and Cloths</string>
    <string name="types_of_services_available">Types of Services Available</string>
    <string name="types_of_cloths_available">Types of Cloths Available</string>
    <string name="ironing">Ironing</string>
    <string name="laundry">Laundry</string>
    <string name="washing">Washing</string>
    <string name="express">Express</string>
    <string name="legal_details_documents">Legal Details/Documents</string>
    <string name="is_your_shop_gst_registered">Is your Shop GST registered?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="do_you_charge_5_gst_as_shop_services_on_all_clothes">Do you Charge 5% GST as shop services on all clothes?</string>
    <string name="gst_details">GST Details</string>
    <string name="enter_gst_number">Enter GST Number</string>
    <string name="pan_details">Pan Details</string>
    <string name="enter_pan_number">Enter Pan Number</string>
    <string name="legal_entity_name">Legal Entity Name</string>
    <string name="address_legal_entity">Address Legal Entity</string>
    <string name="upload_image">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="shop_license">Shop License</string>
    <string name="enter_license_number">Enter License Number</string>
    <string name="bank_details">Bank Details</string>
    <string name="enter_bank_account_number">Enter Bank Account Number</string>
    <string name="enter_ifsc_code">Enter IFSC Code</string>
    <string name="click_on_it_to_upload_license_image">Click on it to upload License Image</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="inventory">Inventory</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="text_spaces">&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="order">Order</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="picked_up">Picked Up</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="contract_and_onboarding_fees">Contract and Onboarding Fees</string>
    <string name="upload_shop_image">Upload Shop Image</string>
    <string name="name">Name:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_order">NewOrderActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="rs">Rs</string>
    <string name="cloth">Cloth</string>
    <string name="cloth_image">Cloth Image</string>
    <string name="steam_ironing">Steam Ironing</string>
    <string name="dry_cleaning">Dry Cleaning</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="mens">Mens</string>
    <string name="womens">Womens</string>
    <string name="kids">Kids</string>
    <string name="enter_bank_name">Enter Bank Name</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email ID</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="pincode">PinCode</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="accepted">Accepted</string>
    <string name="picked">Picked</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="order_idnjsdgjsdjsdvn">order_idnjsdgjsdjsdvn</string>
    <string name="picked_up_date">Picked Up Date:</string>
    <string name="delivered_date">Delivered Date:</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="this_year">This Year</string>
    <string name="this_month">This Month</string>
    <string name="this_week">This Week</string>
    <string name="total_orders">Total Orders :</string>
    <string name="total_earning">Total Earning :</string>
    <string name="_10">10</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="order_no">Order No</string>
    <string name="date_pickup">Date Pickup</string>
    <string name="time_pickup">Time Pickup</string>
    <string name="date_delivery">Date Delivery</string>
    <string name="time_delivery">Time Delivery</string>
    <string name="cloth_name">Cloth Name</string>
    <string name="_2_20">2 * 20</string>
    <string name="cloth_lists">Cloth Lists</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="no_new_order">No New Order</string>
    <string name="terms_condition"><b>TERMS AND CONDITIONS</b>
        \n
        Welcome to www.Launderup.com <b>(“Website”, “Site”, “Application”, Company)</b>, to use
the Services of Company or by any of its affiliates, the entity <b>(“You”, “Your”, “User”,
            “Customer”)</b> must agree to the following conditions. If you visit through this Website, you
accept these conditions.
        \n
Your access to, and browsing, review and use of this Website is subject to these Terms and
Conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and using the Site, you accept the Terms and
Conditions, without limitation or qualification. If you do not agree to the Terms and Conditions,
do not use this Site. If, at any time, any of the Terms and Conditions is no longer acceptable
by you, immediately terminate your use of the Site.
        \n
<b>LAUNDERUP (“Company”)</b> is providing cheapest laundry services whilst connecting the
shop-keepers, individual, entity, organizations and customers to avail the services of laundry.
The ultimate aim of our Company is to create database, provide cheapest laundry services and
connect Customer to the laundry service providers in their proximate locality.
        \n
You hereby agree to the general Terms and Conditions sets forth herein, to avail the laundry
services by connecting through the Company (“Services”). The Services offered by the
Company through their official Mobile Application - www.Launderup.com.
        \n
<b>1. PRIVACY</b>
Please review our Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to our Application, to fully
understand our practices.
        \n
<b>2. ELIGIBILITY</b>
The Services of the website are available only to persons who are competent to enter into a
legally binding contract under the law of republic of India or other applicable jurisdiction,
including un-discharged solvents, minors etc are not eligible for the Services provided by the
Company and hence shall not register as a User or transact to this Website.
In the event of Corporate entity, you represent and warrant that you have the legal authority to
bind such corporate entity to the terms and conditions, in which case the terms “You”, “Your”,
“User” or “Customer” shall refer to such corporate entity.
        \n
        <b>3. ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS</b>
        \n
        <b><i>A. LEGAL SATISFACTION</i></b>
When you visit www.Launderup.com or send emails to us, you are communicating with us
electronically.
        <b><i>B. CONSENT</i></b>
By communicating with us, you consent to receive communications from us electronically.
We will communicate with you by e-mail, WhatsApp or by newsletters.
        \n
        <b>4. SITE ACCESS</b>
This Site grants you a limited access to the laundry services and the Customer can buy such
Services and adept the information, database, offers, coupons, etc.
        \n
        <b>5. WARRANTY</b>
The Company and its affiliates attempt to be as accurate as possible for the Services. The
database as well as other information of the laundry service providers are authentic to be able
to provide laundry Services to the Customer. However, the Company makes no warranties
that the content/information on the Application are error-free. We take the responsibility to
evaluate the best possible content and Services of high standard for the Customers.
        \n
        <b>6. COPYRIGHT</b>
        \n
A. Copyright Protection
All content included on this Application, such as text, graphics, logos., button icons, images,
audio clips, digital downloads, data compilation, and software is the property of this Website
or its affiliates and protected by the Copyright laws and international copyright laws. The
compilation of all content, information, news and others on this Site is the exclusive property
of the Company and protected by the copyright laws. All software used on this Site is the
property of the Company or its software suppliers and protected by the copyright laws.
        \n
        <b><i>B. FALSE INFORMATION</i></b>
You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise
mislead as to the origin or other misinformation. The Company reserves the right (but not the
obligation) to remove/suspend or terminate any Customer, if found, any fraud committed by
the Customer.
        \n
        <b><i>7. OBLIGATIONS AND TERMS:</i></b>
As a condition to using any of Company\'s services, and for the mutual benefit of both Company
and the Customer, the undersigned ("Customer") agrees to the following terms and conditions:
 All garments, clothes, linen, fabrics shall be the responsibility of the laundry service
provider (“laundry shop-keepers”).
 The Company only connects the Customer and the laundry shop-keepers at a reasonable
rate and also be responsible for providing elite class service for laundry by launching
monthly package subscriptions. The 18% GST (Gross-Service Tax) shall be applicable.
 The Company shall ensure that washing, drying and folding services are maintained at a
high level of quality by the laundry shop-keepers.
        \n
        <b>8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</b>
IN NO EVENT SHALL LAUNDERUP, ITS AFFILIATE, AND ALL THIRD-PARTY
SERVICE PROVIDERS, BE LIABLE TO THE CUSTOMER OR ANY OTHER PERSON
OR ENTITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING ANY THAT MAY
RESULT FROM:
 The articles (garments, clothes, linen, fabrics of any kind) which belongs to the Customer
and to which the local laundry service provider will be directly liable, the Company shall
not, in any circumstances, be liable towards the Customer and the local laundry service
provider;
 Company does not hold any liability on account of damages occurred of any kind from the
content published on our Website.
        \n
        <b>9. RELATIONSHIP</b>
This Terms of Use/Terms and Conditions shall not be construed to create any partnership,
joint venture, employer employee, agency, or franchisor-franchisee relationship between the
Company and Customer.
        \n
        <b>10. NOTICES</b>
All notices / communications shall be given to us by email to Launderup@launderup.com.
Such notice will be deemed received in full on a business day and on the next business day if
the email is sent on a weekend or public holiday.
        \n
        <b>11. LAW AND JURISDICTION</b>
These terms and conditions and the relationship between the Customer, service provider and
the Company shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the Law of India and the
Customer and service provider agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of
New Delhi.
        \n
        <b>12. SITE POLICIES, MODIFICATION, AND SEVERABILITY</b>
Please review our other policies, such as our Privacy Policy, posted on our Application. These
policies also govern your visit to this Application. We reserve the right to make changes to
our Site, policies, and these Conditions of Use at any time. If any of these conditions shall be
deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be deemed
severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition.
        \n\n
        <i>[Company Name – LaunderUp]</i>
        <i>[Email - Launderup@launderup.com]</i> </string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_terms_and_condition">I Agree to terms and condition</string>
</resources>